mohela.com 2005-02-07

# MOHELA Privacy Policy

| **General Info**  
---  
  
  Loan Programs  

  Other  
|  **MOHELA Privacy Policy**  
MOHELA Privacy Policy |    
---  
_Our Commitment_  
MOHELA is committed to protecting and respecting the privacy of our customers. We will strive to maintain your privacy and ensure the confidentiality of the information you submit to us.   
   
_Information We Collect_  
We collect and retain information about you only when we reasonably believe that the information will assist us in providing quality loan products, borrower benefits and services to you and in managing your account(s). One of the main reasons we collect certain information is to protect your account(s) and to identify you. The information we collect will also be used to comply with laws and regulations that may apply to us as well as in helping us improve our loan products, borrower benefits and services. We collect nonpublic personal information about you from the following sources:

  * Information we receive from you on applications or other forms;
  * Information about your transactions with us or others; and
  * Information we receive from a consumer reporting agency,
  * Information we receive from nonaffiliated third parties, such as your school and guarantor of your loan.

We do not intend to collect information from children under 13 years of age. If we learn that we have inadvertently collected personal identifying information from a child under the age of 13, we will take all reasonable steps to ensure that this information is deleted from our files.  
   
_Information We Disclose_  
We recognize that you care about how the personal information you have entrusted to us will be handled. We do not disclose any nonpublic personal information about our customers or former customers to anyone, except as permitted by law. We do not share medical or health information except to process transactions or to provide services you have requested or initiated.   
   
_Nonaffiliated Third Parties_  
We do not sell or share customer information to nonaffiliated third parties for the third parties to use for their own purposes. We do share information with companies that work for us. For example, we may disclose nonpublic personal information about you, as permitted by law, to nonaffiliated third parties such as companies that service our loans and/or provide loan servicing computer support. These companies are acting on our behalf and are obligated to maintain the information they receive in a confidential manner. They are never authorized to use the information for any other purposes. We may disclose all of the information we collect, as described above, to companies that perform marketing services on our behalf or to other financial institutions with whom we have joint marketing agreements.  
   
_Security_  
We restrict access to nonpublic personal information about you to those employees who need to know that information to provide products or services to you. We maintain physical, electronic and procedural safeguards that comply with federal regulations to guard your nonpublic personal information.  
   
Internet Privacy Policy
